https://www.fusion-inc.com/privacy-policy/

COVID-19 Update: Open for business with safety precautions – CLICK HERE for more information
Satellite Paste Applicators
Guns, Reservoirs, Nozzles,
Acc.
R-100 Lg. Capacity Reservoir
Automatic Machines
Automatic Brazing Machines
Fixed Station Braze Mate
Braze Mate 100/150/200 Standard Features:
Rotary Index
Rotary Index 100/120 Standard Features:
Satellite Paste Applicators
Guns, Reservoirs, Nozzles,
Acc.
Privacy Policy
Our privacy policy explains:
What information we collect and why we collect it.
How we use that information
Your privacy matters to Fusion Inc.
Please do take the time to get to know our practices.
This website uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.
If you prefer, you may opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads by using the Ads Settings.
You can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin. You can also set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page.
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.
When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
* To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
* To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
* To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
* To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for appointments may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your appointment, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
We use cookies to keep track of visitor site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
Any changes made to our privacy policy will be posted on this page.
Fusion owns a division, Fusion Systems Group, which builds custom automated machines.
LOCATIONS
Fusion Inc.Willoughby, OH USA1 (800) 626-9501(440) 946-3300info@fusion-inc.com
Fusion Incorporated UK LtdHarlow, United Kingdom+44 (0) 1279 443 122infoeurope@fusion-inc.com
© 2020 Fusion Incorporated. All rights reserved.
